junkmail.co.ke 2014-11-22

# Junk Mail Kenya - Privacy Policy

Junk Mail is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you a powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Junk Mail Kenya Web ([www.junkmail.co.ke](http://www.junkmail.co.ke/)) site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Junk Mail Kenya website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

Junk Mail Kenya collects personally identifiable information during the optional registration and ad placement processes, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Junk Mail Kenya also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your postal code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favourites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Junk Mail Kenya. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Junk Mail Kenya for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Junk Mail Kenya Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the Junk Mail Kenya public message boards or classified listings, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Junk Mail Kenya may monitor Communication Services provide on the Junk Mail Kenya website, such as replies to advertisers submitted via the online contact forms. Junk Mail Kenya reserves the right to terminate the User’s access to any or all of the Communication Services at any time without notice for any reason whatsoever.

Junk Mail Kenya encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Junk Mail Kenya so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Junk Mail Kenya is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the www,junkmail.co.ke web site and the Junk Mail (PTY) LTD family of Web sites.

**Use of your Personal Information**

Junk Mail Kenya collects and uses your personal information to operate the Junk Mail Kenya Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Junk Mail Kenya also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Junk Mail Kenya and its affiliates. Junk Mail Kenya may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Junk Mail Kenya does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Junk Mail Kenya may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Junk Mail Kenya may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Junk Mail Kenya, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Junk Mail Kenya does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Junk Mail Kenya keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Junk Mail Kenya, in order to determine what Junk Mail Kenya services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customised content and advertising within Junk Mail Kenya to customers whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Junk Mail Kenya will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Junk Mail Kenya or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Junk Mail Kenya; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Junk Mail Kenya, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

The Junk Mail Kenya web site uses "cookies" to help you personalise your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalise Junk Mail Kenya pages, or register with the Junk Mail Kenya site or services, a cookie helps Junk Mail Kenya to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as contact numbers, your region and so on. When you return to the same Junk Mail Kenya Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Junk Mail Kenya features that you have customised.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Junk Mail Kenya services or other Web sites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

Junk Mail Kenya secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Junk Mail Kenya secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Third Party Cookies**

Junk Mail Kenya use both our own (first party) and partner companies’ (third party) cookies to support these activities. First party cookies are owned & created by the website you’re viewing, ie.e. [www.junkmail.co.ke](http://www.junkmail.co.ke/). Third party cookies are owned & created by an independent company, usually a company providing a service to the website owners. Examples of usages for third party cookies are web analysis (e.g. Google Analytic) and search queries.

Junk Mail Kenya takes due care when selecting 3rd Party service providers, however Junk Mail Kenya cannot take responsibility for the content and use of the cookies deployed by such 3rd parties. You again have the ability within your browser to specifically deny 3rd party cookies.

**Changes to this Statement**

Junk Mail Kenya will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Junk Mail Kenya encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Junk Mail Kenya is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

Junk Mail Kenya welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Junk Mail Kenya has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Junk Mail Kenya at [support@junkmail.co.ke](mailto:support@junkmail.co.ke). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
